♪♪
♪ We're talking away ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm to say ♪
♪ I'll say it anyway ♪
♪ Today's another
day to find you ♪
♪ Shying away ♪
♪ I'll be coming for
your love, okay? ♪
♪ Take on me, take on me ♪
♪ Take me on, take on me ♪
♪ I'll be gone ♪
♪ In a day or two ♪
♪ So needless to say ♪
♪ I'm odds and ends
but I'll be ♪
♪ Stumbling away ♪
♪ Slowly learning that
life is okay ♪
♪ Say after me ♪
♪ It's no better to
be safe than sorry ♪
♪ Take on me, take on me ♪
♪ Take me on, take on me ♪
♪ I'll be gone ♪
♪ In a day or two ♪
♪ Oh, things that
you say, yeah ♪
♪ Is it life or just to
play my worries away? ♪
♪ You're all the things
I've got to remember ♪
♪ You're shying away ♪
♪ I'll be coming
for you anyway ♪
♪ Take on me, take on me ♪
♪ Take me on, take on me ♪
♪ I'll be gone ♪
-♪ In a day ♪
-♪ Take on me ♪
♪ Take on me, take me on,
take on me ♪
-♪ I'll be gone ♪
-♪ Take on me ♪
-♪ In a day ♪
-♪ Take on me, take me on ♪
♪♪